<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Man pages on Stacked Git</title>
    <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Man pages on Stacked Git</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://stacked-git.github.io/man/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>stg-branch(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-branch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-branch/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-branch - Branch operations: switch, list, create, rename, delete, …​
SYNOPSIS stg branch stg branch [--merge] &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; stg branch {--list,-l} stg branch {--create,-c} &amp;lt;new-branch&amp;gt; [committish] stg branch {--clone,-C} [new-branch] stg branch {--rename,-r} [old-name] &amp;lt;new-name&amp;gt; stg branch {--protect,-p} [branch] stg branch {--unprotect,-u} [branch] stg branch {--delete,-D} [--force] [branch] stg branch --cleanup [--force] [branch] stg branch {--describe,-d} &amp;lt;description&amp;gt; [branch] DESCRIPTION Create, clone, switch, rename, or delete StGit-enabled branches.
With no arguments, the current branch is printed to stdout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-clean(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-clean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-clean/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-clean - Delete empty patches from the series
SYNOPSIS stg clean [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION Delete the empty patches from the entire series by default, or only empty patches from the applied or unapplied patches. A patch is considered empty if its tree is the same as its parent.
OPTIONS -A --applied Delete empty applied patches
-U --unapplied Delete empty unapplied patches
StGit Part of the StGit suite - see linkman:stg[1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-commit(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-commit/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-commit - Finalize patches to the stack base
SYNOPSIS stg commit [OPTIONS] [patch]…​ stg commit [OPTIONS] -n &amp;lt;number&amp;gt; stg commit [OPTIONS] --all DESCRIPTION Finalize one or more patches into the base of the current stack and remove them from the series. This is the opposite of linkstg:uncommit[]. Use this command when a patch is completed and no longer needs to be managed with StGit.
By default, the bottommost patch is committed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-completion(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-completion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-completion/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-completion - Support for shell completions
SYNOPSIS stg completion bash [OPTIONS] stg completion fish [OPTIONS] stg completion zsh [OPTIONS] stg completion list aliases [OPTIONS] stg completion list commands [OPTIONS] stg completion list commands-and-aliases [OPTIONS] stg completion list help aliases stg completion list help commands stg completion list help commands-and-aliases stg completion list help help stg completion man [OPTIONS] stg completion help bash stg completion help fish stg completion help zsh stg completion help list aliases stg completion help list commands stg completion help list commands-and-aliases stg completion help man stg completion help help DESCRIPTION Support completions for bash, fish, and zsh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-delete(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-delete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-delete/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-delete - Delete patches
SYNOPSIS stg delete [OPTIONS] [&amp;lt;patch&amp;gt;…​] stg delete [OPTIONS] [-A] [-U] [-H] stg delete [OPTIONS] --all stg delete [OPTIONS] --top DESCRIPTION Delete patches
OPTIONS -a --all Delete all patches
-A --applied Delete the applied patches
-U --unapplied Delete the unapplied patches
-H --hidden Delete the hidden patches
-t --top Delete topmost patch
--spill Delete the patches, but without modifying the index and worktree. This only works when deleting applied patches at the top of the stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-diff(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-diff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-diff/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-diff - Show a diff
SYNOPSIS stg diff [OPTIONS] [path]…​ DESCRIPTION Show the diff (default) or diffstat between the current working copy or a tree-ish object and another tree-ish object (defaulting to HEAD). File names can also be given to restrict the diff output. The tree-ish object has the format accepted by the linkstg:id[] command.
OPTIONS -r &amp;lt;revspec&amp;gt; --range=&amp;lt;revspec&amp;gt; Show diff between specified revisions. Revisions ranges are specified as rev1[.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-edit(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-edit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-edit/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-edit - Edit a patch
SYNOPSIS stg edit [OPTIONS] [patch] DESCRIPTION Edit a patch. Various aspects of a patch may be edited, including the message, author, patch name, or even the patch’s diff.
By default, the topmost patch is edited.
With no options or when --edit is specified, the patch details are edited interactively. Alternatively, command line options may be used to modify the patch non-interactively.
The --diff option causes the patch’s diff to be appended to the patch description when editing interactively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-email(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-email/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-email - Format and send patches as email
SYNOPSIS stg email format [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;patch&amp;gt;…​ stg email format [OPTIONS] --all stg email send [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;file|directory&amp;gt;…​ stg email send [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;patch&amp;gt;…​ stg email send [OPTIONS] --all stg email send --dump-aliases stg email help format stg email help send stg email help help DESCRIPTION Format and send patches as email.
A typical workflow is to first generate email files for each patch along with an optional cover letter using stg email format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-export(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-export/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-export/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-export - Export patches to a directory
SYNOPSIS stg export [OPTIONS] [patch]…​ DESCRIPTION Export a range of patches to a given directory in unified diff format. All applied patches are exported by default.
Patches are exported to patches-&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; by default. The --dir option may be used to specify a different output directory.
The patch file output may be customized via a template file found at &amp;#34;$GIT_DIR/patchexport.tmpl&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;~/.stgit/templates/patchexport.tmpl&amp;#34;, or &amp;#34;$(prefix)/share/stgit/templates&amp;#34;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-files(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-files/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-files - Show files modified by a patch
SYNOPSIS stg files [OPTIONS] [revision] DESCRIPTION Show the files modified by a patch. The files of the topmost patch are shown by default. Passing the --stat option shows the diff statistics for the given patch. Note that this command does not show the files modified in the working tree and not yet included in the patch by a refresh command. Use the diff or status commands to show these files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-float(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-float/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-float/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-float - Push patches to the top, even if applied
SYNOPSIS stg float [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;patch&amp;gt;…​ stg float [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;-S|--series&amp;gt; &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; DESCRIPTION Push patches to the top, even if applied.
Float one or more patches to be the topmost applied patches. The patches to be floated may currently be either applied or unapplied. The necessary pop and push operations will be performed to float the named patches. Patches not specified will remain applied or unapplied as they were prior to the float operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-fold(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-fold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-fold/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-fold - Fold diff file into the current patch
SYNOPSIS stg fold [OPTIONS] [file] DESCRIPTION Fold diff file into the current patch. The given GNU diff file (or standard input) is applied onto the current patch.
With the --threeway option, the diff is applied onto the bottom of the current patch and a three-way merge is performed with the current top. With the --base option, the diff is applied onto the specified base and a three-way merge is performed with the current top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-goto(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-goto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-goto/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-goto - Go to patch by pushing or popping as necessary
SYNOPSIS stg goto [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;patch&amp;gt; DESCRIPTION Go to patch by pushing or popping as necessary
OPTIONS -k --keep Keep the local changes
-m --merged Check for patches merged upstream
--committer-date-is-author-date Instead of using the current time as the committer date, use the author date of the commit as the committer date.
--conflicts[=&amp;lt;policy&amp;gt;] Either &amp;#34;allow&amp;#34; or &amp;#34;disallow&amp;#34; pushing a patch with conflicts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-help(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-help/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-help - Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s)
SYNOPSIS stg help branch --list stg help branch --create stg help branch --clone stg help branch --rename stg help branch --protect stg help branch --unprotect stg help branch --delete stg help branch --cleanup stg help branch --describe stg help clean stg help commit stg help completion bash stg help completion fish stg help completion zsh stg help completion list aliases stg help completion list commands stg help completion list commands-and-aliases stg help completion man stg help delete stg help diff stg help edit stg help email format stg help email send stg help export stg help files stg help float stg help fold stg help goto stg help hide stg help id stg help import stg help init stg help log stg help name stg help new stg help next stg help patches stg help pick stg help pop stg help prev stg help pull stg help push stg help rebase stg help redo stg help refresh stg help rename stg help repair stg help reset stg help series stg help show stg help sink stg help spill stg help squash stg help sync stg help top stg help uncommit stg help undo stg help unhide stg help version stg help help DESCRIPTION Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-hide(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-hide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-hide/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-hide - Hide patches in the series
SYNOPSIS stg hide [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;patch&amp;gt;…​ DESCRIPTION Hide patches in the series.
Hidden patches are no longer shown in the plain series output.
OPTIONS -b &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; --branch=&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; Use &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; instead of current branch
StGit Part of the StGit suite - see linkman:stg[1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-id(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-id/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-id - Print git hash of a StGit revision
SYNOPSIS stg id [OPTIONS] [revision] DESCRIPTION Print the hash (object id) of a StGit revision.
In addition to standard Git revision specifiers (revspecs), patches may be specified in the form [&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt;:]&amp;lt;patch&amp;gt; or [&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt;:]{base} for the base of a stack. If no branch is specified, the current branch is used by default. The parent of a patch may be specified with [&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt;:]&amp;lt;patch&amp;gt;^.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-import(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-import/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-import/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-import - Import patches to stack
SYNOPSIS stg import [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;diff-path&amp;gt; stg import [OPTIONS] -m [&amp;lt;mail-path&amp;gt;|&amp;lt;Maildir-path&amp;gt;] stg import [OPTIONS] -M [&amp;lt;mbox-path&amp;gt;] stg import [OPTIONS] -S [&amp;lt;series-path&amp;gt;] stg import [OPTIONS] -u &amp;lt;diff-url&amp;gt; stg import [OPTIONS] -u -m &amp;lt;mail-url&amp;gt; stg import [OPTIONS] -u -M &amp;lt;mbox-url&amp;gt; stg import [OPTIONS] -u -S &amp;lt;series-url&amp;gt; DESCRIPTION Import patches from various sources to the stack.
The simplest usage is to import a diff/patch file into the stack from a local file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-init(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-init/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-init/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-init - Initialize a StGit stack on a branch
SYNOPSIS stg init [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION Initialize a StGit stack on a branch.
Initializing a branch with a StGit stack commits initial, empty stack state for the branch to the repository. Theses stack metadata commits are tracked by the refs/stacks/&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; reference. Updated stack state is committed by each StGit command that modifies the stack. StGit users do not have to do anything with the refs/stacks/&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; ref directly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-log(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-log/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-log/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-log - Display or optionally clear the stack changelog
SYNOPSIS stg log [OPTIONS] [--] [patch]…​ stg log --clear DESCRIPTION Show the history of changes to the stack. If one or more patch names are given, only the changes affecting those patches are shown.
The linkstg:undo[] and linkstg:redo[] commands may be used to step back and forth through historical stack states. The linkstg:reset[] command may be used to reset the stack directly to a historic state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-name(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-name/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-name - Print patch name of a StGit revision
SYNOPSIS stg name [OPTIONS] [revision] DESCRIPTION Print the patch name of a StGit revision.
Try to get the name of the patch in the current branch as specified by a StGit revision. Revisions can be specified in the all the forms accepted by &amp;#34;stg id&amp;#34; command.
OPTIONS -b &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; --branch=&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; Use &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; instead of current branch
--showbranch Display the branch name with the patch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-new(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-new/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-new - Create a new patch at top of the stack
SYNOPSIS stg new [OPTIONS] [patchname] [-- &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;…​] stg new [OPTIONS] [--name &amp;lt;patchname&amp;gt;] [-- &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;…​] DESCRIPTION Create a new, empty patch on the current stack. The new patch is created on top of the currently applied patches, and is made the new top of the stack. Uncommitted changes in the work tree are not included in the patch — that is handled by stg-refresh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-next(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-next/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-next - Print the name of the next patch
SYNOPSIS stg next [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION Print the name of the next patch.
The next patch is the unapplied patch that follows the current, topmost patch. An error message will be printed if there are no unapplied patches.
OPTIONS -b &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; --branch=&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; Use &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; instead of current branch
StGit Part of the StGit suite - see linkman:stg[1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-patches(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-patches/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-patches/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-patches - Show patches that modify files
SYNOPSIS stg patches [OPTIONS] [path]…​ DESCRIPTION Show the applied patches modifying the given paths. Without path arguments, the files modified in the working tree are used as the paths.
OPTIONS -b &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; --branch=&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; Use &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; instead of current branch
-d --diff Show the diff for the given paths
-O &amp;lt;option&amp;gt; --diff-opt=&amp;lt;option&amp;gt; Pass additional &amp;lt;option&amp;gt; to git diff.
See the linkgit:git-diff[1] man page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-pick(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-pick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-pick/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-pick - Import a patch from another branch or a commit object
SYNOPSIS stg pick [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;source&amp;gt;…​ stg pick [OPTIONS] [--name NAME] [--parent COMMITTISH] &amp;lt;source&amp;gt; stg pick [OPTIONS] --fold [--file PATH]…​ &amp;lt;source&amp;gt;…​ stg pick [OPTIONS] --update &amp;lt;source&amp;gt;…​ DESCRIPTION Import one or more patches from another branch or commit object into the current series.
By default, the imported patch’s name is reused, but may be overridden with the --name option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-pop(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-pop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-pop/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-pop - Pop (unapply) one or more applied patches
SYNOPSIS stg pop [OPTIONS] [patch]…​ stg pop [OPTIONS] --all stg pop [OPTIONS] -n &amp;lt;number&amp;gt; DESCRIPTION Pop (unapply) one or more applied patches.
By default, the topmost applied patch is popped.
If ranges of patches are specified, pop and push operations are performed such that only the patches specified on the command line are unapplied at the end of the operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-prev(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-prev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-prev/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-prev - Print the name of the previous patch
SYNOPSIS stg prev [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION Print the name of the previous patch.
The previous patch is the applied patch preceding the current, topmost patch. An error message will be printed if not enough patches are applied.
OPTIONS -b &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; --branch=&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; Use &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; instead of current branch
StGit Part of the StGit suite - see linkman:stg[1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-pull(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-pull/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-pull/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-pull - Pull changes from a remote repository
SYNOPSIS stg pull [OPTIONS] [repository] DESCRIPTION Pull the latest changes from a remote repository.
The remote repository may be specified on the command line, but defaults to branch.&amp;lt;name&amp;gt;.remote from the git configuration, or &amp;#34;origin&amp;#34; if not configured.
This command works by popping all currently applied patches from the stack, pulling the changes from the remote repository, updating the stack base to the new remote HEAD, and finally pushing all formerly applied patches back onto the stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-push(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-push/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-push/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-push - Push (apply) one or more unapplied patches
SYNOPSIS stg push [OPTIONS] [patch]…​ stg push [OPTIONS] -n &amp;lt;number&amp;gt; stg push [OPTIONS] --all DESCRIPTION Push one or more unapplied patches from the series onto the stack.
By default, the first unapplied patch is pushed.
Unapplied patches may be pushed in arbitrary order, but out of order pushes may result in merge conflicts. If there are conflicts while pushing a patch, the conflicts are written to the work tree and the push command halts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-rebase(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-rebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-rebase/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-rebase - Move the stack base to another point in history
SYNOPSIS stg rebase [OPTIONS] [committish] DESCRIPTION Pop all patches from the current stack, move the stack base to the given new base and push the patches back.
Merge conflicts may arise when patches are being pushed-back onto the stack. If this occurs, resolve the conflicts and then continue the rebase with the following sequence:
stg add --update stg refresh stg goto top-patch Or to skip the conflicting patch:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-redo(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-redo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-redo/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-redo - Undo the last undo operation
SYNOPSIS stg redo [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION If the last command was an undo, the patch stack state will be reset to its state before the undo. Consecutive redos will undo the effects of consecutive invocations of linkstg:undo[].
It is an error to redo if the last stack-modifying command was not an undo.
OPTIONS -n &amp;lt;n&amp;gt; --number=&amp;lt;n&amp;gt; Undo the last &amp;lt;n&amp;gt; undos
--hard Discard changes in the index and worktree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-refresh(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-refresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-refresh/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-refresh - Incorporate worktree changes into current patch
SYNOPSIS stg refresh [OPTIONS] [path]…​ DESCRIPTION Include the latest work tree and index changes in the current patch. This command generates a new git commit object for the patch; the old commit is no longer visible.
Refresh will warn if the index is dirty, and require use of either the --index or --force options to override this check. This is to prevent accidental full refresh when only some changes were staged using git add interactive mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-rename(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-rename/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-rename/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-rename - Rename a patch
SYNOPSIS stg rename [OPTIONS] [old-patch] &amp;lt;new-patch&amp;gt; DESCRIPTION Rename [old-patch] to &amp;lt;new-patch&amp;gt;. If [old-patch] is not given, the topmost patch will be renamed.
OPTIONS -b &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; --branch=&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; Use &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; instead of current branch
StGit Part of the StGit suite - see linkman:stg[1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-repair(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-repair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-repair/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-repair - Repair stack after branch is modified with git commands
SYNOPSIS stg repair [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION If a branch with a StGit stack is modified with certain git commands such as linkgit:git-commit[1], linkgit:git-pull[1], linkgit:git-merge[1], or linkgit:git-rebase[1], the StGit stack metadata will become inconsistent with the branch state. There are a few options for resolving this kind of situation:
Use linkstg:undo[] to undo the effect of the git commands. Or similarly use linkstg:reset[] to reset the stack/branch to any previous stack state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-reset(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-reset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-reset/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-reset - Reset the patch stack to an earlier state
SYNOPSIS stg reset [--hard] [&amp;lt;committish&amp;gt; [&amp;lt;patchname&amp;gt;…​]] stg reset --hard DESCRIPTION Reset the patch stack to an earlier state. If no state is specified, reset only the changes in the worktree.
The state is specified with a commit id from the stack log, which may be viewed with linkstg:log[]. Patch name arguments may optionally be provided to limit which patches are reset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-series(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-series/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-series - Display the patch series
SYNOPSIS stg series [OPTIONS] [-A] [-U] [-H] stg series [OPTIONS] --all stg series [OPTIONS] --short stg series [OPTIONS] [patch]…​ DESCRIPTION Show all the patches in the series, or just those in the given range, ordered from bottom to top.
The topmost applied patch is prefixed with &amp;gt;. All other applied patches are prefixed with +. Unapplied patches are prefixed with - and hidden patches with !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-show(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-show/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-show - Show patch commits
SYNOPSIS stg show [OPTIONS] [patch-or-rev]…​ [-- &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;…​] stg show [OPTIONS] [--patch &amp;lt;patch-or-rev&amp;gt;]…​ [-- &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;…​] stg show [OPTIONS] [-A] [-U] [-H] [-- &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;…​] DESCRIPTION Show the commit log and diff corresponding to the given patches. The topmost patch is shown by default, or HEAD if no patches are applied. The output is similar to linkgit:git-show[1].
OPTIONS -p &amp;lt;patch-or-rev&amp;gt; --patch=&amp;lt;patch-or-rev&amp;gt; Patch or revision to show</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-sink(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-sink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-sink/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-sink - Move patches deeper in the stack
SYNOPSIS stg sink [OPTIONS] [patch]…​ DESCRIPTION Move the specified patches down the stack.
If no patch is specified on the command line, the current (topmost) patch is sunk. By default, patches are sunk to the bottom of the stack, but the --above or --below (alias --to) options may be used to place them above or below any applied patch.
Internally, sinking involves popping all patches to the bottom (or to the target patch if --above or --below is used), then pushing the patches to sink, and then, unless --nopush is specified, pushing back any other formerly applied patches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-spill(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-spill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-spill/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-spill - Spill changes from the topmost patch
SYNOPSIS stg spill [OPTIONS] [path]…​ DESCRIPTION Spill changes from the topmost patch. Changes are removed from the patch, but remain in the index and worktree.
Spilling a patch may be useful for reselecting the files/hunks to be included in the patch.
OPTIONS -a &amp;lt;note&amp;gt; --annotate=&amp;lt;note&amp;gt; Annotate the patch log entry with note
-r --reset Also reset the index such that the patch’s changes only remain in the worktree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-squash(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-squash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-squash/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-squash - Squash two or more patches into one
SYNOPSIS stg squash [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;patch&amp;gt;…​ DESCRIPTION Squash two or more patches, creating one patch with their combined changes.
The squash process, at a high level:
Pop all the given patches, plus any other patches on top of them.
Push the given patches in the order they were given on the command line. This establishes a tree containing the combined changes from the given patches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-sync(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-sync/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-sync/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-sync - Synchronize patches with a branch or a series
SYNOPSIS stg sync &amp;lt;--ref-branch=BRANCH|--series=SERIES&amp;gt; [&amp;lt;patch&amp;gt;…​|--all] DESCRIPTION For each of the specified patches, perform a three-way merge with the same patch in the specified branch or series. The command can be used for keeping patches on several branches in sync. Note that the operation may fail for some patches because of conflicts. The patches in the series must apply cleanly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-top(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-top/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-top/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-top - Print the name of the top patch
SYNOPSIS stg top [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION Print the name of the top patch.
The topmost patch is the currently applied patch. An error message will be printed if no patches are applied.
OPTIONS -b &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; --branch=&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; Use &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; instead of current branch
StGit Part of the StGit suite - see linkman:stg[1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-uncommit(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-uncommit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-uncommit/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-uncommit - Convert regular Git commits into StGit patches
SYNOPSIS stg uncommit &amp;lt;patchname-1&amp;gt; [&amp;lt;patchname-2&amp;gt; …​] stg uncommit -n number [&amp;lt;patchname-prefix&amp;gt;] stg uncommit -t &amp;lt;committish&amp;gt; [-x] DESCRIPTION Convert one or more Git commits from the base of the current stack into StGit patches. The original Git commits are not modified; the StGit stack extends to incorporate these commits as the bottommost applied patches. This is the opposite of linkstg:commit[].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-undo(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-undo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-undo/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-undo - Undo the last command
SYNOPSIS stg undo [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION Reset the patch stack to the state before the last operation. Consecutive undos will go back to yet older stack states.
OPTIONS -n &amp;lt;n&amp;gt; --number=&amp;lt;n&amp;gt; Undo the last &amp;lt;n&amp;gt; commands
--hard Discard changes in the index and worktree
StGit Part of the StGit suite - see linkman:stg[1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-unhide(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-unhide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-unhide/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-unhide - Unhide hidden patches
SYNOPSIS stg unhide [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;patch&amp;gt;…​ DESCRIPTION Unhide hidden patches in the series.
Hidden patches are no longer shown in the plain series output.
OPTIONS -b &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; --branch=&amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; Use &amp;lt;branch&amp;gt; instead of current branch
StGit Part of the StGit suite - see linkman:stg[1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg-version(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-version/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg-version/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg-version - Print version information and exit
SYNOPSIS stg version [OPTIONS] DESCRIPTION Print version information and exit
OPTIONS -s --short Show abbreviated version information
StGit Part of the StGit suite - see linkman:stg[1]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stg(1)</title>
      <link>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stacked-git.github.io/man/stg/</guid>
      <description>NAME stg - Manage stacks of patches using the Git content tracker
SYNOPSIS stg [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;command&amp;gt; […​] stg [OPTIONS] &amp;lt;-h|--help&amp;gt; stg --version DESCRIPTION StGit (Stacked Git) is an application that provides a convenient way to maintain a patch stack on top of a Git branch:
The topmost (most recent) commits of a branch are given names. Such a named commit is called a patch.
After making changes to the worktree, you can incorporate the changes into an existing patch; this is called refreshing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
